Lewes
You're the only one who can save me now
Sell your frogs to me
So I won't have to pay triple
the breach penalty
And you get paid too
It's a win-win
Oh
How much are you offering
Fifty
Four hundred thousand
Nice calculation
The cost of my frogs alone
Is already four hundred thousand
You expect me to work for free
In your dreams
I'll add another
One hundred thousand
Lewes
We are family
You wouldn't profit off me
I indeed shouldn't profit off you
So I'm not selling my frogs to you
You
If you can't handle Mr. Lewes then get lost
Don't hold up our business talk
Lewes
I failed to recognize
your greatness just now
Please don't hold it against me
What exactly do you want
I want to buy your frogs
At three hundred a piece
As many as you have
Three hundred
Each
That's higher than Daniel's
Original purchasing price
Didn't Daniel say
That Lewes doesn't know how to raise frogs
How come his own frogs died
While Lewesg's are fat and strong
I bet
The reason he made money before
Was all thanks to Lewes
How is this fair
That loser Lewes
How could he raise such good frogs
The frogs
I'm not selling
Why
Do you mind that we
Worked with Daniel before
We
We were all scammed by him
We are victims too
Right
We were all fooled by him
He talked a good game
Saying
The technician is a top university grad
And the frogs raised
Would definitely be
better than the last batch
But they ended up looking like toads
Covered in sores
I will never work with him again
Not only will I cut ties with him
I'll also tell my peers
To blacklist him across the industry
Boss Lewes
How about this
Can you sell the frogs to us now
No
Sir
This was truly an accident
Please don't blacklist me